metmodels.com 2019-05-13

# MetArt - Privacy

Last Changes to Privacy Policy: May 24, 2018

We are strongly committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. The policies below are applicable to the MetArt Network family of websites which are listed in Schedule A below and any other websites that display this Privacy Policy, however accessed and/or used, whether via personal computers, mobile devices or otherwise, and other interactive features, applications or downloads that are operated by us that are available through these websites and post this Privacy Policy (collectively "Website") produced and maintained by SARJ, LLC. ("Company" or "we", "us", or "our"). We have established this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to let you know how we handle your Personal Information (as defined below). This Privacy Policy also describes the rights and options available to you with respect to your personal information. 

Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy apply to information gathered online at our Website and offline through your interactions with us outside of the Website. It does not apply to information collected by websites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we may link and which you choose to use, subject to these websites’ privacy policies.

By visiting our Website, you are accepting the practices described in our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website. We may revise our Privacy Policy from time to time and if we do, we will make an effort to notify you of these changes, including through a banner on the Website’s homepage, and we will include the latest version of the Privacy Policy in the link provided for it on the Website. Your continued use of our Website and our affiliate sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. If we intend to apply the modifications or amendments to this Privacy Policy retroactively, we will provide you with notice of the modifications or amendments.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or don't see your concerns addressed here, you should contact us by email at [privacy@metartnetwork.com](mailto:privacy@metartnetwork.com).

Controllers of Personal Information

The Company is a Washington  limited liability company with a principal place of business at  [800 Stewart St, Seattle, WA 98101](https://www.google.com/url?q=https://opengovus.com/washington-corporation/603508899&sa=D&ust=1527276198191000)

If you reside or are located in the European Economic Area ("EEA") the Company is the data controller of all Personal Information collected via the Website, as set out in this Privacy Policy.

The Purpose of this Privacy Policy

We adhere to the highest standards of ethical practices in all of our operations and are dedicated to protecting the privacy of all visitors to our Website. Our privacy policy is simple: Except as disclosed below, we do not use or sell, barter, give away, or rent your personal information to any company outside of Company.

What Personal Information Does this Privacy Policy Cover?

So that we can provide you with the most efficient and enhanced experience, you must register for a personal account accessible through a confidential password and nickname that you select. We collect personal information ("Personal Information") about you for the following stated purposes:

For purposes of registration and use of our services, we collect Personal Information about you such as your name, user ID and email address and may collect telephone numbers, address, billing information (which may include credit card number, credit card security number, bank routing number, and bank account number), IP address, unique device identifier, and demographic information such as age, gender and zip code.

We also collect and store information that you enter into this Website or that you provide through our help desk, or to any customer service representatives, in conjunction with requests for more information.

Personal Information may also be collected if there are certain portions of the Website in which you specifically and knowingly provide such information, e.g. community postings (i.e., chat or bulletin boards, forums, blog comments, video reviews, if any). If you submit information for a model submission, we may collect Personal Information such as your name, address, driver's license number, date of birth, email address, and any other information visible on the photo identification you provide.

We also may collect, combine and store information about you that we receive from other sources or from affiliated websites, to enable us to update and correct the information contained in our database.

Analytical Information

In addition, when you interact with the Website, for statistical and analytical use, our servers may keep an activity log about your use of the Website ("Analytical Information"). Generally, this information is collected through "traffic data." We collect and store certain administrative and traffic information with each use of the service or Website including: source IP address, access location, time of access, date of access, web page(s), software crash reports, type of browser used, screen resolution, language, session identification number, search terms, search results, access times and referring websites addresses.

Use of Cookies and Spyware

We never use or install spyware on your computer or device, nor do we use spyware to retrieve information from your computer or device.

Like many websites, we use "cookies," which are small text files that are stored on your computer or equipment when you visit certain online pages that record your preferences. We use cookies to track use of our Website and online services. We may also use cookies to monitor traffic, improve the Website and make it easier and/or relevant for your use. You may occasionally get cookies from companies advertising on our behalf. We do not control these cookies, and these cookies are not subject to this Privacy Policy.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but, if you prefer, you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. For more information on cookies and how to disable them, you can consult the information provided by the Interactive Advertising Bureau at www.allaboutcookies.org.

This Website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics may also use cookies to help us analyze how users interact with and use the Website, compile reports on Website activity, and provide other services related to Website activity and usage. The cookies may collect information such as your IP address, time of visit, whether you are a return visitor, and any referring website. The information generated by Google Analytics will be transmitted to and stored by Google and will be subject to Google's privacy policies.

Like some Websites, we may use web beacons. A web beacon (also known as "action tags" or "single-pixel gifs") is an invisible graphic on a web page that is programmed to collect non-personally identifiable information about your use of a given website. Like cookies, web beacons allow Company and its technology providers to summarize overall usage patterns for our analysis and provide personalized services and advertising content. We do not share or provide Personal Information we may collect through such web beacons, such as names, e-mail addresses and phone numbers with our advertisers without your express permission.

Is Information Collected From Children?

This Website is not directed to children under the age of 18, and Company does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 18 years of age. If you are under 18 years of age you should not use this Website, and under no circumstance should you provide Personal Information to Company. If Company discovers that a child under the age of 18 has provided Company with Personal Information, Company will immediately delete that child's information.

How Do We Use Your Personal Information?

We use your Personal Information to help us personalize and continually improve your experience on the Website. For example, we may use the information to present you with content, products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. We use Personal Information to handle subscription orders, deliver products and services, process payments, communicate with you about orders, products, services, promotional offers, update our records and generally maintain your accounts and relationships with us. We also use this information to improve our Website and platform, prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our Website and, as described below, enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf. Except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy, we do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to our Website or your Personal Information collected online to any companies not affiliated with us.

Customer Service and Feedback

We may also use your Personal Information to fulfill orders, provide customer service, track your compliance with the Website's rules and regulations, or for editorial and feedback purposes (to the extent that is explained when you provide the information).

Use of Anonymous Information

We use Anonymous Information to help us determine how people use parts of the Website and who our users are so we can improve our Website and ensure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many people as possible. We also use Anonymous Information to provide statistical "ratings" information in aggregated form to our partners and other third parties about how our users collectively use the Website. We may also use or share Anonymous Information (or other information, other than Personal Information) in any other manner that we deem appropriate or necessary.

Third-Party Agents

We will share your Personal Information with our service providers who assist us with the internal operations of the Website. These companies are authorized to use your Personal Information only as necessary to provide these services to us and not for their own promotional purposes. We do not sell your Personal Information to third parties. A detailed list of those service providers is listed below in Schedule B. We also use third party agents to manage payment processing on the Website. If you make a purchase on the Website, you will be directed to a third party payment processing website, and the practices described in this Privacy Policy for Company do not apply to information gathered on such website. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of the third party payment processing website.

Emergency Situations

We may also use or disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to applicable law or comply with legal process served on us or the Website; (b) protect and defend our rights or property, the Website or our users, and (c) act under emergency circumstances to protect the personal safety of us, our affiliates, agents, or the users of the Website or the public.

Government Authorities, Legal Rights and Actions.

We may share your Personal Information with various government authorities in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; to establish or exercise our legal rights or to protect our property; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases we reserve the right to raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us. We also may share your Personal Information when we believe it is appropriate to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of the Company, the Website, our users, customers, or others; and in connection with our Terms of Use and other agreements

Retention of Personal Information

If you reside or are located in the EEA, we keep your Personal Information for no longer than necessary for the purposes for which the Personal Information is processed. The length of time we retain Personal Information for depends on the purposes for which we collect and use it and/or as required to comply with applicable laws and to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights.

What Steps are Taken to Keep Personal Information Secure?

The importance of security for all Personal Information associated with you is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your device to our servers. Personal Information collected by our Website is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose Personal Information to you.

While we try our best to safeguard your Personal Information once we receive it, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

External Links

For your convenience we may provide links to websites operated by organizations other than the Company that we believe may be of interest to you. Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy for Company do not apply to information gathered through these other websites. These other sites may also send their own cookies to you, collect your data or solicit your Personal Information. Always be aware of where you end up. We are not responsible for the actions and privacy policies of third parties and other websites. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave this Website and read the privacy policies of each and every website that you visit.

What About Contests and Sweepstakes?

When we run a contest or sweepstakes relating to this Website, it will be accompanied by a set of rules. The rules for each contest/sweepstakes will specify how the information gathered from you for entry will be used and disclosed, if it is different than as described in this Privacy Policy. In conjunction with your entry in such contest or sweepstakes, Personal Information will be collected only if you voluntarily submit it to our sponsors or us.

Public Areas, Chat Rooms and Comments

Please remember that any information you share in public areas, such as message boards, chat rooms or feedback sections, becomes public, and therefore this Privacy Policy does not apply to any information you choose to make public. Please be careful about what you disclose and do not post any Personal Information that you expect to keep private.

Change of Ownership

We may change our ownership or corporate organization while providing the Website and services. As a result, please be aware that we may transfer your information to another Company that is affiliated with us or with which we have merged. Under such circumstances Company would, to the extent possible, require the acquiring party to follow the practices described in this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended from time to time.

International Data Transfers

The Website is primarily operated and managed on servers located and operated within the United States. In order to provide our products and services to you, we may send and store your Personal Information (also commonly referred to as personal data) outside of the country where you reside or are located, including to the United States. Accordingly, if you reside or are located outside of the United States, your Personal Information may be transferred outside of the country where you reside or are located, including to countries that may not or do not provide the same level of protection for your Personal Information. We are committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of Personal Information when it is transferred. If you reside or are located within the EEA and such transfers occur, we take appropriate steps to provide the same level of protection for the processing carried out in any such countries as you would have within the EEA to the extent feasible under applicable law.. If you are located in a country outside the United States of America and voluntarily submit Personal Information to us, you thereby consent to the general use of such information as provided in this Privacy Policy and to the transfer of that information to, and/or storage of that information in, the United States of America.

Changes to This Privacy Policy

We are committed to maintaining our position as a premier Website on the Internet. As our Website continues to develop, we may add new services and features to our Website. In the event that these additions affect our Privacy Policy, this document will be updated appropriately. We will post those changes prominently so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. We do, however, recommend that you read this Privacy Policy each time you use the Website in case you missed our notice of changes to the Privacy Policy. We will never, however, materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information we have previously collected without your express consent.

Updating or Deleting Your Personal Information

You have certain rights in relation to your Personal Information. If you would like further information in relation to your rights or would like to exercise any of them, you may also contact us via [privacy@metartnetwork.com](mailto:privacy@metartnetwork.com). If you reside or are located in the EEA, you have the right to request that we:

  * provide access to any Personal Information we hold about you;
  * prevent the processing of your Personal Information for direct-marketing purposes;
  * update any Personal Information which is out of date or incorrect;
  * delete any Personal Information which we are holding about you;
  * restrict the way that we process your Personal Information;
  * provide your Personal Information to a third party provider of services; or
  * provide you with a copy of any Personal Information which we hold about you.

We try to answer every email promptly where possible, and we will provide our response within the time period stated by applicable law. Keep in mind, however, that there will be residual information that will remain within our databases, access logs and other records, which may or may not contain your Personal Information. Please also note that certain Personal Information may be exempt from such requests in certain circumstances, which may include if we need to keep processing your Personal Information to comply with a legal obligation.

When you email us with a request, we may ask that you provide us with information necessary to confirm your identity.

How Do I Opt-Out or Correct Information About Me

You may always opt-out of receiving future e-mail messages and newsletters from Company. We provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about you. We also give you access to a broad range of information about your account to permit you to correct or update Personal Information that you have previously provided to us. To do so, you can send us a message at support@metart.com.

Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Company who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [privacy@metartnetwork.com](mailto:privacy@metartnetwork.com).

Schedule A

List of the MetArt Network Family of Websites

MetArtNetwork.com

MetArt.com

Met-Art.com

MetArtX.com

metart.com

VivThomas.com

TheLifeErotic.com

ErroticaArchives.com

EroticBeauty.com

LoveHairy.com

Domai.com

GoddessNudes.com

MyErotica.com

Live.tv

ALSScan.com

RylskyArt.com

EternalDesires.com

Stunning18.com

MyErotica.com

Schedule B

List of Sub-Processors

SARJ, LLC

Streamate

CCBill

Payoneer

Rocketgate

Epoch

GoCoin

Google Analytics

Sendgrid

Mailgun

Mouseflow

Pingdom

GMail

Apple

Youtube

Zendesk

Slack

Facebook

Twitter

Instagram

Tumblr

Medium

Telegram

Pinterest

VKontact

Highwinds

Amazon

Bico Pacific

Flirt4free

IMLive

Nubiles

Erika Lust Films

DatingGold

FlushCash

Fuckbook

Gamelink

International Media Company

NVGArt

Medley

MindGeek

Mr Skin

Penthouse

Penthouse FFN

Playboy

SexSearch

Shaft

TrafficPartner

UpForIt

Vodafone

VideoBox

Videosz

VSMedia

Wet and Puffy
